guys fall is here you're excited yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah we weather the swimming crisis
over summer only for an autumn challenge to rear its ugly head i'm aware it sucks
are they holding a week over there the party's here and he has his class's sports day team assignments
oh yeah oh wait do i not hand them off to you guys or no you do
feels as if sports day creeps closer and closer every time a class turns in a form hate to break
it to you pal but it is getting closer every time
uh let's pray for a raid let's do a rain dance
hey everyone our roster's ready what's going on
is
we
Thank you.
Okay. Good luck to you.
I said our dust.
Iyorta and Yuki are also on the East team.
You're kidding me.
Those gung-ho teammates.
No way am I going to be able to stay out of sight and do nothing.
Such a loaded confession, yet spoken so casually.
I thought he was absent, but he was just slacking off.
Oh, the girls are performing a cheer routine, right?
Will you be cheering too, Sakura?
Will I cheer?
Yes, I will.
Even if we possess no sense of rhythm at all, it's mandatory.
Hey, your voice went down a few octaves.
Gotta make our pom-poms, yeah?
Indeed.
I hope our routine isn't too hard.
I haven't even asked if you're East or West.
West, thankfully.
Remy is too.
Meaning we'll be rivals.
At least you'll have Toru and Miyamura.
I'm on the same team as Ishikawa.
And he's going to see me out there flailing like an idiot!
Can rhythmless people rain dance, you think?
Yes!
Come and sit with me!
Rain dance!
Is the student council okay?
What's his deal?
I mean, the guy's been a klutz since we were little kids, sure.
But as our student council president, he has got to suck it up!
So I take it his clumsiness didn't make him much of an athlete, huh?
Not at all.
Always crying and falling down.
It'd be nice if he could take a page out of Sota's book.
You think?
Because I, uh...
Hmm.
I don't have any good sports day memories either, so I sympathize.
Hmm?
You're lightning on your feet, which makes you a great competitor for the hundred meter!
Don't get me, bleh!
What you should be giving is your all!
Because I intend to give it the exact same.
So absolutely zero slacking or else!
As far as sports go, I'm really not that gifted either.
But I think I'll surpass last year.
Call it a hunch.
You honestly want me to go all out in that race?
Mm-hmm.
And you want me to cheer when I'm on the sidelines?
Yep, that's right!
Then when I take the field, will you cheer for me?
Of course I will, duh!
We're on different teams, though.
Well, yeah, I know that.
But I'll still be watching.
Right.
How strange.
I wanted it to be over as soon as possible before.
But now I'm genuinely looking forward to it.
Yo, Miyamura!
Can I swing by tomorrow night?
Sorry, but no.
Gotta prep for sports day.
Really?
My school held our sports day back in June.
What events are you doing?
Or are you skipping?
I'm still debating, but I might do the 100-meter dash.
Maybe.
Oh.
Someone sounds motivated.
Yeah.
Surprisingly, I am.
Wow, cool.
Might have to come see this passion firsthand.
No, don't you dare.
I'd be willing to bet anything.
The days ahead will be a bit crazier than usual.
That's it for today, girls.
Good work!
It's so hard.
I'm the only one having trouble with the moves.
I'll be as humiliated as I was last sports day.
Maybe more.
Because this year, Ishikawa could see me make a fool of myself.
Hey there, Kono.
Yoshikawa.
Are you all right?
You aren't feeling sick, are you?
No, that's not it.
Okay, then what's wrong?
Guess I'm wiped from practicing our cheer routine.
Oh my gosh, we had practice and I squeezed.
Oh, I'm a West team member, so you should be fine.
Gotcha.
Hope the East didn't rehearse.
There's not a sporty bone in my body.
And I have no rhythm.
Cheering takes a toll on me.
Never mind.
Forget I said any of that.
I think I'll practice a little extra before heading home.
Right pump.
Then left goes twice.
Then right.
Or was it left again?
Um, that looks like the part both teams do.
Yeah.
Right first.
Huh?
When your right hand goes up, put your left to your chest.
Do it with me.
Sure.
Next, do two pumps on the left.
Then turn your whole body and throw a left punch.
Oh, right, the punching part.
Put both hands up and shakey shake shake.
One, two, three, four.
Great punch.
Now let's shakey shakey shake.
Wait, I thought those two were on opposing teams.
I'd rather not do the cheer.
See?
Killing it.
Thanks to you.
As long as they're having fun.
I have nothing but love for Sengoku and Remy.
I really do.
All you had to do was mix.
You're mad, aren't you?
Whatever emotion I may be processing now is entirely beside the point.
Should Remy mix in this?
You have to read the labels more carefully or risk botching the entire thing.
Wait, that isn't right.
Try this stuff here.
No!
Apart from reading the labels, you have to read the recipe as well, Sengoku.
It's getting everywhere!
Though it says salt, is it actually salt or something else?
Most things labeled salt are going to be salt, okay?
And why is our workstation messier than a death scene from a horror movie?
Their group isn't done mixing in the ingredients yet?
Class is just about over.
Chop the veggies, Sengoku.
You can handle that, right?
Me?
With...
With weaponry?
Kill it!
I've slipped my mind.
How slippery is your mind to not see the skin?
What's Remy doing?
Are you a killer?
You hereby lose all knife privileges!
Remy wants to slice up that she's two.
Then learn how to hold kitchen knives!
I'm gonna have nightmares about that sight for a week!
You just stir this very carefully while I add in the ingredients.
Nothing less and not a smidge more, okay?
Oh, just stirring?
Pizza cake!
Ow!
I cut me!
At least it's small, though.
Wash it with soap and then we'll get you a bandage.
Oh, right.
Come on, soldier.
Let's patch you up.
Sakura!
Hey!
Think this is good?
Looks yummy!
Time to add that stuff in.
Wait, why is it all wibbly?
Are you finished?
Is it supposed to look this way?
It's smoking like a chimney!
Quick, we need ventilation!
It's making my eyes stink!
Open the windows!
Oh!
Even now, the memories of our last cooking class haunt me.
Look me in the eye.
But you're angry!
Look at me so you understand!
What will we be making today?
Curry!
Good.
Now what ingredients did you bring?
A radish.
Why, though?
Tofu?
But why?
Are daikon radishes included in the curry you eat at home, Sengoku?
Well, uh, no.
I don't believe they are.
Then what's it doing here?
The only time I've seen curry, it's been fully cooked in the pot and ready to go.
Wasn't sure how to stir it, but the radish felt like a good choice.
Any veggie you actually see in curry would have been a better choice.
Then placing all those vegetables around the pot slowly brings forth the curry.
No, we're cooking it!
Our entire class lowered their standards and picked curry in hopes you would be able to do this.
Okay, if not curry, what can you make?
Pasta?
Croquettes?
The prepackaged food you simply have to unwrap and warm up doesn't qualify as a dish you make.
I-I know that.
Luckily, I brought stuff too, so let's start by cutting up the-
Ah!
Your knife privilege was revoked!
I want you to pay very close attention to what you're doing, Sengoku.
He-he's gotten better!
Wow, when did you become an expert peeler, huh?
Awesome job!
Once peeled, we'll-
Um, the potato disappeared.
Cause you whittled it to nothing!
The onion disappeared too!
You're supposed to stop peeling at some point!
Thank goodness our classmates saw this coming.
All the other groups donated a portion of their curry to us.
They know us too well.
Sengoku will be in charge of heating the pot.
Remy can plate the rice while we wait.
Will dreams be the only place I went at cooking?
Work hard enough, and those dreams will come true.
Why in the world are the flames so high?
High heat means high flames.
No way!
That was high heat?
You lied!
What did you do?
Sakura?
I mean, try, but she's so sorry.
The rice means about it and it's a girl.
Please don't cry.
Just let it go.
Rice girl is fine, yeah?
We have to eat runny rice girl with gooey curry now!
Yes, bon appetit.
Hey, it's pretty good.
Isn't it, Remy?
Yeah, wish the rice was cooked all the way, though.
Thanks a lot for sharing.
It's totally cool, I promise.
Hope things turn out better next time.
I'm sorry, again.
Remy's a failure.
No, you aren't.
We all have things we don't really excel at.
One thing you'll excel at is being someone's wife!
Cooking isn't the only thing that makes or breaks a spouse.
You can't deny it's definitely an advantage.
So what should Remy do?
No soul on earth will want to marry me.
Me either.
No cooking skills, no wedding rings.
Don't you worry.
If nobody else will have you,
I'll take both your hands in marriage.
No way!
Thank you, Sakura!
You're so cool!
Come out his boyfriend material.
Ta-da!
Sports day t-shirts!
All of his shirts are over there.
This one here's a medium.
What size are you?
A medium?
No, uh, I'm a large.
So small.
Let's save the smalls for girls.
No mercy for the West!
I'm just blaring with you.
Who's gonna pick up this pushover slack?
So absolutely zero slacking or else, Miyamoto!
That sounds like something that pushover over would say.
Way too many overs.
Hey, Yoshikawa.
Hmm?
There a large West shirt in there?
Sure is.
Shouldn't you be helping me since you're also on the committee?
I want my shirt too.
Got any East smalls?
Yoshikawa, where are the West mediums?
Oh, yeah.
And can I get a West small?
Is this a joke?
You needy jerks!
Get your help!
Well, anyway, what sports day events did you sign up for?
I went with the hundred meter dash.
You could always join the relay.
What?
No, that's too much pressure.
Members of the track team compete in that one.
Not exclusively, though.
Back when he was a first year, Shu participated.
And was thoroughly smoked, of course.
Well, at least the East has the president on their side.
Truth.
Honestly, that alone should be enough to up our odds, huh?
Really hoping he doesn't decide to play hooky.
This sports day will be our last one.
He'll come.
Please, rain!
Guys have to do top of the pole, and there's also the mock cavalry battle.
Apart from those and cheering, the rest is all co-ed.
And speaking of, cheer practice looks rough.
But there's a payoff for that hard work.
Haughty, you look great.
OFD, so thinkin' cool!
Really?
You have to wear that.
Well, Miyamoto, you like?
I feel betrayed.
Not really what I had in mind.
Listen up, cause this can get confusing.
In this particular sentence, this noun here gets modified.
Got it?
Remember, a modifying noun is more information about the...
It's the return of the Ice Queen.
You're with me so far?
If so, you're looking for both seconds to...
I hear spirits knocking.
Now, next to read is...
Ori.
That's mine.
Um, ease up on the emotion and translate it, if you please.
Get away from her, dummy.
And where are you pulling that from?
I swear, she forgot her book is all.
Yeah, so?
So, for today, I let her share mine.
Oh, please, no!
What are you freaking out about?
The fact that you're furious with me right now?
Hey, you're afraid when I haven't said a word?
I'm not hiding anything at all, Ori.
But you won't believe me.
What?
Of course I believe you, but that's not even what this is about.
Oh, it's, uh...
Oh, never mind.
Jealous Hori is such a scary version of you.
Me? Jealous?
Now, don't be silly, Yuki.
I was more murderous.
For his sake, turn that feeling into jealousy starting today.
Is it just you?
What?
Who acts super jelly?
Does he get like that, too?
Oh, Miyamura.
Um...
It's fine.
Thanks, Yuki.
Look who it is.
Ditto.
For both of you.
Guess the gang's all here.
Almost through with painting, Yoshikawa?
Yeah, just about.
Good. Hear the announcement?
They just called for every third year on the sports day committee to come.
Said we gotta be quick about it, too.
Well, they'll be waiting a while.
I can do this for you.
Aw, you...
What grade did you manage to pull in our class?
Look, that's not relevant, so just get going and leave this to me.
Thank you, Hori.
I'll hurry right back after, okay?
Mm-hmm.
All I have to do is stay inside the lines.
Easy enough.
Don't need an A in art to do this, Yuki.
Achoo!
I wish I thought to wear my blazer today.
I bet.
This fall weather has been pretty chilly.
Mizuuchi.
You're so lucky.
I would kill for a pair of pants right now.
Wait.
Won't be so cold if you keep that over your lap.
Just give it back when you're done.
Um, hey, one minor thing.
I might get pain on it.
Hi, Hori.
Ah!
Done yet?
Thanks for the jump scare.
And no, I'm not done.
Who's is that?
Mizuuchi's?
I said I'd kill for some pants, and...
He gave me this.
Uh...
It's warmer than the blazer.
Yeah, well, I have been wearing it, so that makes sense.
Thank you.
How is he gonna know?
I guess that's true.
You wanna give me a hand?
Don't think I've ever painted like this before.
Oh, but you went outside the line here.
Uh...
Achoo!
Hori.
You warm?
Yeah, thanks.
This really helped.
Sure you're not cold?
Mm-hmm.
If you need something else, let me know.
Uh...
Yeah, that's right.
Strut away in the exact opposite direction from Hori.
Completely oblivious that it's my body heat you're feeling now.
Honestly...
Are you jealous?
You really are!
You can stop anytime, Giggles.
Huh.
I just saw her drape it over her legs.
But for some reason, the sleeves feel nice and warm, too.
Yeah.
tee has a form of one more.
Wow.
I love it.
Yeah.
Mm-hmm.
Thank you for being here.
Are you all dressed up?
Yeah.
Oh.
See you next time.
Ah,ちゃんと前を向いてるよって言ってくれる君が必要なんだ
Ah,また想いが張り裂けそうなのに
URLより短い言葉にしかできない私です
I'm so sad, don't go on,でも
君に飛べるように
出会えるように
できてたなら